The pinkish rock salt tablet seemed woefully inadequate to the bearded man that had changed
Cole Copperlepper's world.
They hadn't noticed each other at first.
On the long cold journey to the New Fort in the lean early years of Ragdreams, when all
had been dolomite dust and cold berry mush for dinner, he had simply been another dwarf
in the mix.
He was an adequate miner, a decent conversationalist, but not really noteworthy in any respect.
Unlike many of the others, however, he didn't yell at Cole.
Somehow he had recognized that being expedition leader did not truly make her the arbiter
of the Fort's fate.
It might have been his politeness that made her appreciate him at first, or maybe his
pleasant tenor singing voice.
Or maybe it was just his complete and cheerful disinterest in what anyone else thought of
him.