Regardless, it started with shared laughter over the manager's complaints to Cole, overheard
by Vavok one evening in the dining room.
The manager was always complaining.
Nothing pleased him, possibly because he'd inherited the job after his predecessor died
in the great zombie attack of 110, and he had no idea what he was doing.
As its complaints echoed off the unsmoothed walls, Cole felt the familiar exasperation
sinking in, the despair that somehow everything was always her fault.
But Vavok met her eyes and smiled comfortingly.
Gravity shifted.
The inexorable pull of the minds eased, and she felt the knot of volcanic fear and stress
ease, seeing for the first time the calm warmth of his sepia-toned eyes.
Stolen moments turned into a lingering ittle.
They act as though I can stitch the zombies back together, Cole ranted to Vavok one peaceful
night over plump helmet beer.
The same old boos and other sorts of dorvant angst that Cole had to hear about, as if she
could control even the crops.
What do they want me to do?
I'm helping carry the bodies?
I helped mine out the tombs for the truly dead?
I even sorted through that pile of teeth to get the right bits into the right coffin.
They act like I just sit in the depot all day, gossiping with merchants.
What more can I do?
Vavok leaned over and kissed her smooth scalp.
They know you can't fix it, he said.
They don't expect you to fix it, but they trust you with their fears.
Cole took a long pull of her beer.
She could taste the grit of the rock mug through the rough sourness of the mushrooms.
Maybe the dwarves' complaint about the boos was fair.
Maybe she understood.
The words settled into her buried bones.
She found a core of empathy she never knew existed, and listening to the haranguing voices
became a gift she could offer to her fellow settlers.