They mined deeper, as dwarves will.
They began to smooth and engrave their walls and floors in an attempt to create peace and
beauty in their dirty and blood-smeared world.
There was talk of starting a hospital to treat the numerous injuries from the were and zombie
invasions.
No one felt happier, not really, but Cole felt as if she was helping, finally, and that
made the entire world feel lighter.
All because of Babock's warm, gentle presence in her life.
Cole felt herself becoming lighter, too.
Months passed, and uneasy peace settled over their hamlet like a fine mist.
Things occasionally took a turn for the strange, admittedly.
Zombie janitors carted away waste, children played make-believe in the numerous tombs,
peasants, unable to find their calling, created extraordinary artifacts.
And Babock found a battle axe he liked.
He came into the bedroom that morning as Cole shaved her scalp, a daily routine made worse
by the lack of soap and a mirror, but it was what she did and had done for years, and it
made her feel like herself.
He wrapped one arm around her waist, the axe in his other hand, and kissed her on the neck.
Look at this axe, he said.