It's a really great axe," he said.
I just—I really like it.
He gazed fondly at the axe.
As far as Cole could see, it was nothing special.
A battle axe with an avocado-wood handle and a copper blade.
She had bought it herself from the merchants the previous fall, intending it for their
newly formed squad.
But she was very empathetic, and anything Vabok-like she liked, too.
That's—well, that's great, dear," she said meekly.
He beamed at her.
I think I'll take it with me today.
We're digging out that ramp to the water in the second cavern so that the new hospital
can have a well.
Perfect, Cole said, her enthusiasm genuine this time.
The hospital was her idea, and if any miner could get that ramp done, it was Vabok.
And if having this axe with him helped him feel good about the job, all the better for
everyone.