The door banged shut behind him and Cole smiled to herself as she scraped the blade over her
scalp once more.
The news of Vabok's death, rather the news of his ghostly apparition wafting into the
tavern near the caverns, took time to reach Cole, who was sleeping peacefully in her engraved
bedroom, dreaming of the newly engraved temple.
When she woke, she stretched, smiling to herself, warm in the belief that life and rag dreams
had turned a corner.
She stopped in the temple on her way to the tavern, a brief moment to herself to thank
the gods for her blessings.
Sure the zombie preying beside her smelled a bit bad and the manager had yelled at her
again on her way here, but she had a plan to order some better meals from the kitchen
and there were enough yaks to slaughter one for meat and tallow.
Soap at last.
And best of all, she had Vabok with his warm smile and his really great axe.
The good mood carried Cole through the rest of her day, even though lunch was mussel pancakes,
again, and she even felt up to the task when the first reports of the ghost reached her.
Ghosts were nothing new, after all.
After the Weremonitor lizard attacks, most of their resources had gone to entombing the
remains they could identify and engraving slabs to honor those they could not bury.
More than one ghost had spurred them to speed the Enterprise.