Is she a villain, too?
She is a villain.
Yay.
In 21, she became a scout in Groveslings.
In midwinter 21, she fooled the Sword of Warriors
into believing she was the poet Unib Worksmiths
of the Sword of Warriors.
Then in the midwinter of 21, as the poet Unib Worksmith,
she visited Cryptshield to gather intel.
In 29, she became lovers with Zahn Granitslipt.
In 30, she married Zahn Granitslipt.
In 30, she left where she was living with Zahn Granitslipt
and settled in Anguish Iron.
In 31, she fooled the Entangled Realms
into believing she was the monster slayer Onaf Shurok
of the Entangled Realms.
In the early summer of 31,
she visited Fauntel to gather information.
In 42, she became lovers with Massus Diamondclasp
and married Massus Diamondclasp in 47.