Sounds bad.
After he decapitated Grump Gromp the Roach Man.
But he has several more steps to take.
One of those, of course, being Buffy.
He has made quite the impact on the crowd
with his hefty platinum pick, Buffy has.
But Buffy collapsed in a puddle of his own ichor,
swinging wildly.
Ichor?
Ichor.
Swinging wildly with his pickaxe while hoof loomed over him.
Buffy's flailing rapidly weakened, though,
as the flow of ichor from his stump
slow before finally stopping altogether.
Congratulations to Haruf on his victory.
And alas, Yeti stooned to become spaghetti, became spaghetti.
And Dead Death Roll, the reptile man with the axe guitar,
also lost his fight.
Mm, too bad.
So basically everyone we talked about last time
wound up dying this round.
That's OK.