Who cares?
Fiery cities.
Anyway, we're doing well.
We've had a population boom, and now have 86 dwarves in residence.
Oh my.
It was at 77, and then while I was taking notes this afternoon, we got those remaining
nine dwarves.
So, very exciting.
I'm also pleased to report that the mystery of Ral, the dead drunk from last week, has
been solved, because our mayor, that I also talked about last week, Urvad Atulalan, was
also found dead.
And you know, I had started the justice, and there was no mysteries or anything like that,
and then I started getting all these combat notifications, and realized that there was
a giant ulm in the caverns that was fighting with dwarves, and it was named, and I looked
at its kills, and the mystery was solved.
So now we know.
I still don't know why he was just described as drunk, but maybe he was drunk at time of
death, and now that's what he's remembered for.