Yes. I talked a little bit about Rivad's marriage and their 10 children. And I checked in on her
husband to see how he felt about his wife's death. And either he is unaware, or just doesn't care.
Abbas Bellriddles is currently ecstatic. He has the happiest mood. And I noticed is a legendary
metal crafter. He is the one that I had assigned to our metal crafting workshop thingy. And some
of his contributing factors to his good mood are feeling proud of the metal statues he has created
for Wet Ring, and for teaching someone actually, which is something that we'll talk about a little
bit later with Guild Halls. Oh, yeah, that's our topic for today. I guess we didn't mention that
we're going to talk about Guild Halls. He also had, um, I noticed that he had created a something.
So I went into the into Legends mode, because the name of what he was the creator of was cut off in
his character sheet. And it was Grimtaxt the Bronze Earring, his family heirloom, that was
recently destroyed at Wet Ring. Though I didn't ever get a notification or know what happened.
Maybe, maybe his wife was wearing it, and she she died. But I perhaps we'll never know. I looked
it up and couldn't find out. Yeah, yeah. And in further looking him up, he he's quite the guy.
He's like 137. I think he has 18 children, 18, 18, only 10 of which were with the former mayor,
as he was both married and divorced before he met Urvaad.