Oh, yes, I bet it was blocks and I forgot about that damn blocks. Yeah, she needed rock blocks. Oh well
So she she's dead, but we did have some successful artifacts
cog standard fences a stone worker
Created the high rim a limonite crown worth 12,000 more for us. Yeah, that's some skill if it's made out of limonite
It's encrusted it has gold on it
It's encrusted with cushioned limonite cabochons and oval native gold cabochons and decorated with dog bone
Subject menaces with spikes of dog bone and milk quartz and it was fortunate for a cog that I had had to do a mass puppy
Slaughter right before this happened because we wouldn't have had any other bones. I don't think so
Yeah, he got lucky timing wise and then we also had a very boring artifact made by besmar paddled
tramples a gelder
He made the spattered stigma, which is a cool name kind of metal goth a little metal especially coming