They weren't doing much damage or anything, so I've, again, been using cage traps to deal
with these things.
And so I have, it's got to be upwards of 30 different creatures in cages, and I don't
know what to do with them, so I just put them down in the bottom cavern level, and they're
sitting there.
And some of the troglodytes and naked mole dogs have had children and or puppies, and
now those are in the cages.
So we might train some naked mole dogs, I guess.
You can train troglodytes, but I don't want to.
That one weirds me out a little bit.
And let's see.
There was a notification that a hunter was hunting, which is apparently a thing that
you get, and I don't care, but it was really ominous to have it pop up and say, so-and-so,
a hunter is hunting.
Like, what are you hunting?