And then things went really, really badly south very quickly.
So we were just ticking along.
I think I was in the process of starting to make luxury apartments for my dwarves.
And I did the whole like building rooms vertically and you put the stairs and I was engraving
the floors and they were getting all this nice furniture.
And they were everyone was actually pretty happy.
I'm looking at a screenshot from when that happened and there were 53 dwarves.
27 were yellow, meh, you know, totally neutral.
Two were the one slightly more orange than that and everybody else happy.
They're all good.
And then I got the following message.
The were monitor, fences, sybilisk, roods, okay, all right.
The were monitor has come, a large monitor twisted into humanoid form.
It is crazed for blood and flesh.
Its eyes glow green.
Its charcoal scales are blocky and set far apart.
Now you will know why you fear the night.