It really does.
And same for the way the resource management
is kind of held because there's all these different
unique ones and you're trading them.
And again, the trading in here would make more sense
if you were playing it with three other people, kind of,
and you could trade for what you need
a little bit more efficiently.
So I think there's a lot of board game influence.
Just makes me think a little bit of like Armello,
which was a video game that the designers talked a lot
about how he initially designed it as a board game
or played it as a board game before trying to code it.
I get that feeling here.
Like this feels like a lot of the mechanics
that don't make a whole lot of sense
from a video game city builder point of view
would make more sense as a board game.
So some other mechanics that just kind of show
the complexity of this and how you have so many
intersecting pieces are that as the game goes on,
you unlock more buildings, as we talked about.
Cornerstones, which are kind of bonuses
that you can choose from the queen.
Again, well, you know, I think those, the cornerstones,
do actually have a pretty big game impact frequently.
Yeah, that is an interesting point too,