And then, but those also then factor into,
both the buildings and the cornerstones
factor into the delivery mechanics,
which are part of how you get the reputation
to the renowned to complete a run.
So you really need to hit those deliveries.
And if you don't get the right combination
of buildings, cornerstone, and trade,
and resources and all that,
sometimes you just can't hit those.
And so then you have to go to your secondary win condition,
which again was something not super emphasized
in the tutorial of the resolve of your villagers, right?
Because if your villagers have the resolve
above a certain level, which is different for each race.