Which is... it's just, it's a terrible name.
Rasput.
Just say it like a Russian.
Um, hopefully we're not offending anyone.
Well, so yeah.
And then I had quite a few other logistical problems with this fort to the degree that
I was like, okay, this fort is broken and I'm just going to start a new one.
That ended up not being the case, but some of you probably saw this on stream.
I was feeling like a lot of time had passed without seeing merchants and I really needed
merchants because we need more dwarves, we need other stuff.
And I finally went and looked and the initial merchants traders from our civilization were
stuck on the map.
Like maybe 15 tiles, 20 tiles away from our trading post.