And so I made him statues of water buffalo out of this light blue stone.
I put one in in his office and I gave him light blue furniture and I put light blue
flooring down in his room and another water buffalo statue and he's a little happier.
He likes his bedroom a lot.
Good.
Yeah.
And then the other thing that I did was because he has this whatever bookkeeping skill is
called I bumped him from doing very little of it to a lot of it.
And I don't know if that has helped or not but we have very precise calculations now.
So at any rate he's a little bit happier.
So do you do you know of any other ways like I have the open stockpile so that they can
take things if they want.
I need to explain that.
OK.
The idea between behind the open stockpile is that you make a finished goods stockpile
say stockpile one more time stockpile stockpile and you tell it not to allow bins.
And so things like bracelets rings crowns finished goods.
They're just don't.