in a way.
Yeah.
And I've talked about how I'm not sure how to make an aesthetically pleasing fort, especially
like on the larger scale is one thing, but when you start looking at individual dwarves
and their preferences and then making their bedrooms and things meet those desires, like
it starts to just naturally get prettier.
I think so, yeah.
I also have a lot of colorful stone at this particular fort, so it's nice.
I am glad I persisted because we have so many gems and pretty stone, and even though we
don't have a ton of like, we don't have silver or copper, best I can tell, or we haven't
found it yet, it's still very full of useful things and pretty things.
So I was thinking that I was going to just spend some time this afternoon working on
happiness, but then we got cavern dwellers.
We at least got the alert for them.
I never saw them.
They I guess never ventured into our part of the cavern, so I don't know what they are
yet even when I went to look at the sheet that has everybody who's at your fort and
the invaders.
So that's still a mystery.
I'm not sure what it's going to end up being.
I hope to see something different, you know?