Yeah. So still, still don't know what those are going to be, but, um,
excited to see. And, uh, we got our first forgotten beast this afternoon.
This was, Kamaba has come, a towering feathered porcupine.
It has a knobby trunk and it undulates rhythmically.
Its emerald feathers are downy. Beware its deadly spittle.
And it actually had a really cute sprite. It did have a trunk.
It wasn't green. So we just have to envision it having green feathers.
So this guy came in and he was like, he was zooming along,
like looking for dwarves to murder. Um,
took out four dwarves was eventually killed once they sent the squadron down.
And there were some peasants fighting him who survived,
which is pretty impressive. But after killing him, finally,
I did as you did.
And I built a butcher right next to its carcass and the dwarves just auto
butchered it. And then I, um,
went to check on the tannery and it had Tana hide.
So, um, you said I should look and see what dwarf was hauling it just to make
sure. And we followed her along. She has very sad story,
but I'm not going to get derailed just yet. Uh,
so she made us some forgotten beast leather.
And now I am having someone sew a leather image of
that forgotten beast onto its own hide,
which I feel is fitting.
It's very metal.
That hasn't, I made the order, but it hasn't happened yet.
So I'm excited to see what comes of that.