I mean, that's just another example of how you got to bring your own fun.
Absolutely.
Uh, there has been an interview split into two parts on the Game Maker's
Notebook podcast with Zack and Tarn Adams.
And one of the really noteworthy things that I thought that they said was that
they need these types of stories to be shared because this game is a community
experience.
And I thought that that was so cool and so evocative of what we do and why people
listen to us talk about our forts because like this craziness.
And if you don't have someone who understands, they're just going to look
at you like you are absolutely just batshit crazy.