Yeah, right. I mean I could make it like a really really nice room and put in therapy cats or dogs
or whatever. It would be convenient if she liked one of the animals that we have.
But uh so we still have our Baroness Eryth Rekrok who is the mother of five and survived the initial
demon attack and everything. She is not very happy despite being made Baroness. I think part of it is
that she doesn't really have like a specialty in terms of her labor. So she's not really being
satisfied with anything that she's doing chore-wise or making-wise. And I think she wants
military training but I'm not going to assign one of my nobles to a squad.
She also needs her rooms upgraded and I started working on that today and hopefully that'll
cheer her up. So I gave her some silver furniture like her weapon rack and armor stand are made of
silver and a nice dining room that's all like color coordinated and some quartzite furniture
in there, marble flooring.