Yeah, I suppose. Their dwarf deity is the Hero of Cradling, and there are 96 followers at our fort.
Jeez.
Yeah. The Denomination of Hardiness follows Anoth Gaitnurish as the Symmetric Flag,
who is a human deity and has, I actually don't know how many followers, worshipers they have
in our fort, but they only have 10 in the cult, because those numbers are not necessarily the
same as what we discovered this afternoon. So I guess it's like they're Methodists and Lutherans
and those are different. Anyway, so that's what's happening with the nobility, and I'm going to try
to work to cheer those two up a little bit. I really would like to provide a not super unhappy
ending for that child, but we'll see. I had to exile a couple of our other dwarves that we'd
been following because they were depressed and there was no turning back, and I had replacements
by that point. Sorry, guys. Updating from last week, the animal training continues. You remember
we had some elk birds and I watched the elk bird fail her training and be led to the pasture
repeatedly, and she was just terrified. That's still kind of continuing. Some of them are really
holding on to their training great, and others still wander off and have to be recaught in traps
and refreshed in their training. The Drunians were kind of okay trained, but we were having
food problems and I slaughtered them all. Yeah, it's rough. But on the bright side, the bug bats
have taken swimmingly, flyingly to training, and now we have so many pet bug bats. But I looked at
them and they all belong to one dude. One man. Yes, one man, farmer Sibrek Trade Breaches,
has adopted four bug bats so far. I didn't check when I closed out my fort today to see if he had
adopted any more because when I initially looked at them, he had three and two of them were mated
to each other and had recently had some pups, and then one of them was another adult, and then he
adopted one of the pups. And I was like, who is this weirdo who is so into bug bats? And I looked
up his preferences, and he does indeed like bug bats for their freakish insect heads.