Yeah, and now everything is penguins.
Ah, and then we've also had some attacks that have not been that bad.
We had two in a row, ogre attacks, and we killed them both in minutes.
And I think that the way that I set the fort up has really helped with that,
because we have one entrance that's just one tile wide, and it has a door, and I just lock it.
And then the other one, we have a stone stockpile right by it,
and I just build a wall to close it up as soon as I get the notification that something bad's
happening. Fair enough.
Yeah, and then I've walled us pretty well into the caverns, and we've had serpent people
attacking, and they are, their sprite is fun. They're like a virulent neon gross looking green.