Yes, Nick apostrophe-
A mod belonging to Nick.
Yes.
Okay.
Because Nick wrote in to them suggesting that someone, possibly he, but also whoever, write
a mod to make succession forts easier to do.
Oh, yeah.
And have it be kind of an automated process where people could, you know, check it out,
do it for a year, and then when their year is up, it uploads it back to the server.
Ah, very cool.
And then the next person can download and do theirs and put some sort of like timer
on it so that, you know, if you don't do it, if you don't upload it within a year or two
weeks-
They post to the next one.
Yeah.
And I thought that that was actually pretty cool.
The roundtable guys seemed to think it was pretty cool too.
So hope someone writes that.
Yeah, someone get on that.
Yeah.
If I were a millionaire, I might sit down and just write that tonight.
But yeah.
Yeah.