I think it, I mean, it might exist
and we just don't know about it.
Like embark with no animals or something like that.
Like those kinds of things.
So part of what I'm thinking of with this is with the Sims
and people have over the years come up with all kinds
of like just crazy challenges.
So like, so a Sim that never leaves the lot
which would be really challenging
because you need money and stuff.
Or I remember back in the day it got spread around
that I think it was Rosebud
was the just automatic get a million Gill
and there was mother load for a lot more than that.
And sometimes we just, we being me and my, you know
other teenage friends would just do that
so that we could design fancy houses
and our Sims could have all of the cool stuff
and all of that.
But I mean, it is a cheat, I guess, you know
you have to bring up the cheat code ability
but at the same time, some of these other challenges
that would be genuinely challenging require you
to choose traits or raise your Sims in such a way
that it causes a challenge.
So like telling, preventing Sim parents
from interacting with their children beyond like enough
to keep Sims Child Protective Services
from coming and taking the child away.
And then you have this like.