It's a star they will like. But it is much more magical in the sense of there is magic in the
world. I'm not saying that it's like a more enjoyable, wonderful game in a slangy way.
So you play a character that comes to a village to have a farm and you can fight monsters and mine
and date the people and everything. But in the character creation, there's a lot of customization.
You can play as an elf or a demon or an angel or an elemental. And everyone is very cute or
anime hot. So your romance choices are, they look like anime characters in the art style.
And the pests are baby dragons. It's so cute. And there's a big golden dragon who rules the city.
And for combat, you get spells as well as sword and crossbow and stuff. So I'm really enjoying
it in that it's really flexible in what your character's background is and what your special
skills are from your race and what your focus is. So like, I'm not really big into fishing in any of
these games. So I'm just, I've been able to completely ignore fishing. And I think it's
leveling passively because some quests will give me that regardless. It also has a multiplayer
function. So I will probably force you to play this even though you're not really into the starties.