Okay, a metroidvania is a game where you progress get new items to unlock area to unlock
to unlock uh portions in areas that you've been to previously so you do a lot of backtracking
okay but also it's usually involves pretty creative problem solving with those um tools
that you get okay um so the classic obviously is metroid where you you know get one kind of power
up and that lets you double jump and so now you can get to this whole other set of areas and that
sort of thing yeah um and then castlevania some of the later castlevanias were that way as well
so they're called metroidvanias yeah um in this case it's interesting because it this game monster
sanctuary harkens back to a very very old nintendo game original nintendo game called a boy and his
blob which is where you would go around with as a titular boy with his blob and your blob would
change into different things depending on what kind of jelly bean you fed it