That sounds like something different.
So yeah, that's what went on with KrullKey.
I decided since I had a functioning fort and I could kind of ignore them for a while, that
I was going to experiment with the mist generator thing.
So I made a lot of mistakes.
I was doing this on stream and knew that I could channel out a place where the aquifer
was to create a perpetual pond.
I thought that I would pump the water up from there to a mist generator thing on grates,
with grates on another level and the dwarves could be happy because there's mist but not
puddles.
I'm not sure what I was thinking in that I didn't think there was enough water there
to pump so I had them turn it into a pond thing.