You had gotten actually a pretty good start to it, but the problem when dealing with water in Dwarf Fortress
is that you have to get everything absolutely right or it becomes
problematic quickly.
And you had, I think, missed basically
four squares of smoothing that needed to happen.
So I went and started the... I started kind of from the last point where you had gotten everything smoothed properly.
Mm-hmm. Then I went off in another direction. Mm-hmm.
For, you know, five tiles, whatever.
And then started digging down as well. Hit the aquifer again.
Yeah. And then set the smoothing on each level and what you kind of have to do is
dig out a hole, you know, dig a stair.
Then smooth around and not dig the next stair until that level is smoothed and then do it again and again and again until
they get through the aquifer. Usually ten levels. Okay. And... Wow. That's not fun.