See, there, I did some good Foley work.
There you go.
I had fun with this one because it had a nice personality description.
It has an utterly languid pace of easy living, calm and slow.
It pursues matters with a single-minded focus, often overlooking other matters.
It very easily falls in love and develops positive feelings.
It finds helping others emotionally rewarding.
It tends to consider what others think of it.
It tends to share its own experiences and thoughts with others.
It doesn't often feel envious of others.
It rarely feels discouraged.
It has a tendency to consider ideas and abstractions over practical applications.