So then I took those off and after a bit I realized, maybe about one season in, I realized
that I was running us into the ground in terms of food and drink.
Oh dear.
We're just running completely out.
And I finally looked around and realized the reason for this was I had in the course of
redoing some stuff to use some of the doors and do all of that, I had messed up my manager's
office.
Oh.
The door was open and people were walking through it and I think apparently if he's
trying to work there and people walk through it, it interrupts him at his validating of
the work orders and so food and drink orders weren't getting sent out and all that.
So I fixed up his room and I also kind of forced everybody to start cooking and making
drinks and that started resolving it.