Yeah, I think when I play my year again, I'm going to try to capture something from water
into the glass terrarium because it can hold water and then you can put water creatures in.
Yeah.
What I should do is go find that freaking thief, that freaking thief cave fish man,
fisherman, and lock him.
You mean our neighbor.
Exactly. Lock him into a water terrarium, put him on display as an object lesson for anyone else
who would try to steal from us.
Nice.
The other fun thing was I turned the waterfall back on and we got some decent happiness from
that. I think that's draining good now.
Yeah.
But eventually it did freeze in the winter. And then the giantess Eda arrived, the contested,
and she came and killed a fisher dwarf. And I was a little worried because she was marked as tough.
But that fisher dwarf was then immediately raised by a human monster slayer necromancer.
Wow.
Like literally one turn after she died.