But our squad took care of that really quickly.
So it wasn't a big deal, but I took back over
and was absolutely overwhelmed at the industry
that was thriving from your leadership
and the number of work orders that you had going.
Many of which I canceled because I was having
a really difficult time getting stuff done.
And so you mentioned the office thing,
and I was wondering if the manager was tripped up
because there were so many that were not able
to be fulfilled, like making soap and stuff
once we'd run out of the stuff that it couldn't repeat.
And so every month they're checking it and having to say no
and my gold altars that I wanted to make more temples
were not getting made.