Yeah, so that's a working theory. I don't really know.
But my year was extremely exciting.
So we had two goblin invasions,
so the one that I just mentioned,
and four forgotten beasts.
Four?
Four. One of them was actually a Minotaur,
but I'm counting it as a forgotten beast
because it's just on the outside.
That one was really interesting
because it was killed by one dude who was a bowyer,
and he was just out fishing, and he killed that guy.
He killed Radiant Whispers the Minotaur.
He was just out fishing and ran into this thing
and straight up murdered it.
It was amazing.
So he was injured and got helped off to the hospital.
And unfortunately, I have kind of lost track of him.
If I had... Oh, no, he died.
But I do know he died.
Because we also got made a barony during that last year,
and I definitely would have made him baron,
but he did.
NEXT ON NESFA 그 클래기는ordnung한ís