Ah, but the upside to the grass being dead did give me a direction I decided to take the first year.
Yes.
And that immediately gave me a direction for what I needed to do, which was to get to a cavern as quickly as possible.
The reason for that being, our animals were going to starve if I didn't.
Right.
And so, yeah, year one was devoted, not entirely to digging down to the cavern, but it was devoted a lot of it to digging down to the cavern,
getting some, you know, the usual things to get the stuff up and running with a dwarf fortress going.
Mm-hmm.
Unfortunately, I had to kind of be an elf and make a lot of things out of wood to start with,
because we started in a very sandy, dirty, tree-loamy area.