But then he gave me some lessons and we got it going.
But it was kind of flooding the outside.
So I did, I put in some grates and it's,
you know, maybe one of us will do a YouTube stream
or a Twitch stream and put it on YouTube
and we'll do a tour of our shared fort.
I think that's a good idea.
Yeah, so people can see that then.
And then I was having problems with it
just sort of flooding the outside
so I dug around a little bit
and eventually I just, I turned it off
because it was troublesome.
But then I decided to do what I can do pretty well,
which is to make attractive places for dwarves to hang out.
So I made us a really big tavern
that ended up being called the Gloved Syrups.