Right, like, I understand that you approve of my actions, but I'm a blank slate.
I've said so little to you. But then I just steered into it and I was really glad because
Will's story, while not developed as a personal story, was an excellent world-building story.
So I had this whole sequence where you go into a secret dungeon under the prison in Baldur's Gate
and you find the bones of a dragon that is supposed to be the protector. And, like,
you go into it all hyped, like, yes, I'm gonna have a dragon, I'm fighting on my side.
And you get there and it's dead. And when you go to loot it, because it has the little indicator
that there is stuff, it wakes up and confronts you, not because you're you and the hero, but
because your mind flayer companion is actually the Balderon who was one of the founders with
this dragon of the city.