yeah um well and it's like the the demon guy who was showing up throughout i'm going to pursue that
line in in another playthrough and i'm sure at the time when i do it i will feel like oh my gosh how
did i play the game without this story which does make it very replayable but like that's so much
content it's so much gameplay and uh lucky for them i love re-watching rereading replaying things
so um the the dragon fight for will's quest line actually um is it was one one of the more epic
cool fights to me not just because it's a dragon because the boss had actual like mechanics that
he was doing and like there was one thing that you had to take cover from and these elemental
things that were resistant to certain damages and stuff like that and one of my complaints
about a lot of the fights were just that it was so much trash mobs so many trash mobs so that you
would be you would you know kill the boss and then the next 45 minutes would just be mopping up all
of the like 45 hit point half the hit point of the boss things and i think i would have rather
had fewer tougher enemies than just endless semi-easy