Sorcerer and Warlock are really kind of fuzzy and actually I say I always play Sorcerer
because that's what I play, that's the class in Diablo as well, but when I started this
character I looked long and hard at Warlock too because I hadn't played it and I decided
because of my track record of not finishing video games I should just make my path a little
easier and go with a class that I knew.
And I actually found that while big RPGs like say a Dragon Age or a Divinity, which we tried
and kind of bounced off of, I'm very easily overwhelmed by the interface and the abilities
and it's like just too much to learn and so I'm not committed.
But with this I already knew 5e and I knew what Sorcerer could and couldn't do and I
felt pretty comfortable.