So after the first forgotten beast, we then had our second forgotten beast.
Um, I'm not going to try to say the names.
A huge chicken with, uh, uh, with lidless eyes.
It has a stubby horn and it squirms and fidgets.
It's light brown feathers are long and narrow.
Beware.
It's poisonous.
Sting.
Stinging chicken.
We dealt with that one pretty quick at that point because we had gotten, we had
had a little bit of time between the first one we were able to get people trained up
a little bit enough to fight that.
Then in the same month, the forgotten beast Ascombe has come a towering
feathered click beetle.
It has a square shell and a bloated body.
It's Auburn feathers are long and sparse.
Beware.
It's poisonous.
Bite.
Actually that one we killed in like one fight.
And that was another Chur geek that was taken down with one blow and
they are going to deal with that super Tad Eggman.
Okay, so we've got three shorted beasts left, one weakness, then