No, because then finally the forgotten beast, uh, blah blah blah has come.
A huge eyeless salamander. It has a broad horn and gaunt appearance.
Its pale skin is wrinkled. Beware its webs.
Again, we're back to the webs.
So that one burst up from the bottom of the mines, went through and basically rampaged,
killing the squads that I had assigned to try to hold back any future forgotten beasts.
And, uh, so that took out, I think, probably 15 out of the remaining 60 dwarves.
Then another 25 as it came up the, uh,
and at that point it got to the hospital where everyone recovering from the previous, uh,
forgotten beast fights were currently still recouping.
That then meant that it basically rampaged through that,
killing everyone. And that was the end of the fortress.
Thank you all so much for watching!