That is the current history of the Dimensions of Myth.
Those are the major events for my forts.
But meanwhile, a whole other series of events
have been occurring within the fortress,
within the Dimensions of Myth,
which when you retire a fortress,
or one fails like Sword Begins did,
then you can pull up what's called Legends Mode,
which basically lets you view the entire history of your world
as has happened so far,
including all of the civilizations
that you haven't interacted with.
For an example, besides apparently the goblins
in the Dimensions of Myth,
we do seem to have a problem with kidnapping necromancers,
necromancers who kidnap people,
and then convert the people they've kidnapped
into kind of white walkers or some sort of...