This time I locked the door.
There were still quite a few people outside,
which was a little concerning to me.
But I had a very small squad.
They'd done some training, and I was finally like,
all right, it's now or never, we gotta open the door.
And that was a terrible, terrible, very, very bad idea.
And at that point, you could see the population
of my fort ticking down by the constant new mayors.
And these cave crocodiles just kept going.
And we looked at them a couple of times,
and I think Drew noticed that one of them
was not actually a cave crocodile.
It was the scales of a cave crocodile.
So it's the zombie scales, like a skin, I'm assuming,
dragging itself around, murdering people.
And then there was the arm of a dwarf,
which I'm sure for the dwarves that it killed
was pretty disturbing.