And other times you may get to a place that didn't even look that promising,
but you dig down two layers and you start finding platinum and gold everywhere.
I had one fortress that never even tried to do farming at it,
to make plump elements and make dwarven wine and all of that.
Instead, we had gold basically one layer down, just the seams of it.
Wow.
And so we just made gold crafts and traded everything for that,
and that fort did pretty decently.
Now that was back in one of the older versions.
Right.
But yeah, so it's always open to you to decide what you're going to specialize in,
or if not open to you for anything, it's open to you to figure out,
with the resources I have on hand, what am I going to do.
Right.
Each game is different.