Yeah, I mean, that's exactly right.
To go back to the RimWorld example,
RimWorld does have a thing they call the producer AI,
which within it basically will decide that like,
okay, nothing much has happened,
you've got everything ticking along fine.
So in RimWorld, the producer AI will decide,
okay, you're going to have an invasion now
or something like that.
And Dwarf Fortress doesn't do that.
Dwarf Fortress is pretty,
has a high level of fidelity with its simulation.
Like it all just,
there are rules that they've set up at the beginning
and it just keeps ticking along,
applying those rules rather than kind of doing things ad hoc.
The only thing,
the only ad hoc thing in Dwarf Fortress is you.