You know, I'm still I feel like I'm still kind of learning my way around in in this world.
But I do enjoy checking in.
And I remember I had one my first fort.
People got fae moods just just constantly like that was the only thing that was interesting
about that fort until I later abandoned it.
But there was a child who had gotten into a fae mood and it was after he saw someone who
had gone into a fae mood and didn't have what they need and went berserk and got murdered.
And he was just permanently unhappy after that.
And I just sort of kept an eye on him as things went on and thinking he would do something
interesting and make a bracelet or whatever it was that he made.
And he didn't really. And I did eventually abandon that fort because I felt like I had
my feet under me a little bit better.
But in the next one, I don't think that I followed individuals quite as much.
And I am only a little bit into my third fort.
And I'm still considering kind of what what my angle of approach is going to be, if it's
going to be individual story level or the whole fort or just pursuing the goals of things
that I need to learn. It's open ended, which is, I mean, foreshadowing a little bit of
what we'll talk about later in this episode.