of things.
Oh, okay.
Well, we can trade back and forth a little bit because I have a whole lot to talk about
happening from the Wondrous Planets, specifically Ragdreams, which is still my third fort.
I think we've been going for more than five years, so it's doing okay in that way.
So when I left off last week, everyone was really mad because we'd had that whole wear
monitor thing and then some zombie wear monitors and just some zombies.
So I was trying to figure out ways to make everyone less angry.
So I did some banishing of the angriest, especially after one guy had a tantrum and knocked over
a pedestal that had an artifact on it.
I'm not entirely sure what happened to that artifact after that happened.
I think it might be in a storage bin.
Hopefully someone picked it up who wasn't a thief because we've had some of that happen
too.