I guess we'll come back another day.
But that was just, that one was pretty minor.
The main thing that has been happening still after my last fort is zombies.
So many zombies.
You remember that I lost my last fort to zombies.
I had zombies here and I was wondering about the zombies that just sort of hang around
outside being, they're friendly, but I can't tell them to do anything.
Whereas I have some zombies that are a part of my civilization.
They're productive.
There's one that's a master weaver who does most of my clothes making and another one
made us an artifact actually.
Fair enough.
But the ones that are outside, they're just friendly.
They don't seem to belong to me or to anyone.
And I can't do anything about them.
They're just hanging out out there at the entrance with their guts hanging out.