Well, they could leave and not make my fort ugly because the entrails hanging out and
she just walks around like the same five tiles.
It's yucky.
But most of my resident zombies are not yucky.
I don't see their entrails for the most part.
The artifact that the one made is Ishen Thod, a tower cap mushroom wood door depicting Kogan
Cobalt tattooed ascending to position of king of the robust boulders, which I believe is
something from our history because it had the year four on it.
And I have not interacted with the robust builders that I know of.
Fair enough.
Yeah.
So we also had a lot of other artifacts made by normal dwarfs.
I think the an upside of unhappiness is that we get a lot of strange strange moods.
But then some of those have been stolen because we have a thief problem that I can't seem
to solve.