Right, but I think I might have also found like just rose gold rose gold somewhere
so if you are listening to this and you know the story of rose gold or you can save us a Google and tell us and
Before I swap back to you and then we swap back and you get the biggest news update from rag dreams
I have to say the bat people man those freaking bat people. I think that we're approaching a hundred dead bat people
They just keep swarming up from the caverns and at first they were they were sniping dwarves kind of because you know
It's the caverns. There's lots of corners and lots of people down there gathering cave spider silk and they just get murdered
so
Finally, I was smart and had my squad do a patrol down there
So now every time I get the notification about the bat people, I just send them down to patrol
They take care of business and come back and down in the caverns is like a bat people graveyard
you