Yeah, I feel like the amphibian men are dying a lot more easily than the Batman.
And I noticed that the amphibian men use blowguns, which is funny, especially because I actually
had a dwarf make an artifact blowgun.
Yeah, that's been pretty good.
And I also used the make a burrow in a safe zone and send all your dwarves that aren't
soldiers to the burrow to stay safe while the squad goes and takes care of business.
That worked really well.
My pro tip is don't forget that you assign your dwarves to the burrow or they will dehydrate
and slowly starve to death.
I didn't actually lose anyone to them, but I was just scrolling around going, why is
nobody getting anything done?
Why aren't they digging these tombs?
Why is everybody so hungry and thirsty?
Oh, okay.
And then I, in the moment, I think I was streaming.
So you can probably go to YouTube and watch all this go down.
I just took down the burrow.
I need to reestablish it for further invasions.