No, you'll still see other forgotten beasts because you start out usually in the age of myth
Yeah, which means that of the forgotten beasts that were generated at worldstart at least two-thirds still exist
Yeah, when you go down from two-thirds to one-third of those
You then enter the age of legend
Yeah
And then if you drop down from the one-third down to no forgotten beasts you enter into the age of heroes
Okay
Then if you actually wipe out all the forgotten beasts in your entire world or someone does yeah
Then you begin to enter the ages of the great powers. Oh
so usually that means that you'll start out with the great powers like, you know, the Dwarven and Elven civilizations or
If you're getting down to a really low number of forgotten beasts, but you haven't gotten to zero
You might get something like the age of two powers when a great
Dwarven civilization existed and a great dragon existed. Oh, that's