Absolutely, okay, and this was actually a problem just to give some sort of context to Dwarf Fortress
this was actually a problem in other versions of Dwarf Fortress because
when you let that run for like 350 years if
They if there's a problem with the balancing of the powers of the different races like their abilities and that sort of thing
It's very easy for one race to come to just dominate repeatedly and for a while after necromancer
Necromancers were introduced all worlds would just tend to slide towards
Necromancy right and people would find that if they left it
You know running for more than 200 years or so it's zombies all the way down
It's zombies all the way down. Yeah, just no no recovering and that was kind of boring so
It required some rebalancing, and I think it's a constant point of rebalancing amongst the Tarn and his brother
Yeah, so to go back to the ages okay
We have the age of myth the number of living powers and megabeasts is at least two-thirds of what it was when the world began
the age of legends
One-third of what it was when the world began the age of heroes the number of living powers and megabeasts is greater than three