And that's with a fair number of deaths, with all of the stuff that happened.
Like I said, the webbing titan took out quite a few.
And we are still getting migrants despite the danger, which I enjoy reading.
And in dealing with that, I'm still playing catch up, trying to keep up on the drinks.
That has been a struggle for me at this point, and it's something I'm working on.
Because I think I realized that they had permission to cook with wine and some things.
And every time traders would come, I would be sure to buy whatever alcohol they had,
and we'd just burn through it.
And then I was like, I need to go and check that.
And sure enough, they were making fine meals with wine.
So now that we are not cooking with alcohol, we are only drinking with alcohol.
Hooray!