So that's one need that I've been struggling to keep up with a little bit.
Hopefully it'll be better now.
I've also had some of the clothing problem, which is why we had our little skit about
dwarves taking off their clothes.
And apparently this is an ongoing problem to the point that there are jokes about it
in the wiki.
And the dwarves will indeed take off their clothes when they are worn out and then go
naked to get new ones.
If new ones exist.
Otherwise they'll just be naked and angry.
And they also don't really throw old clothes away.
So you have to kind of make that happen and there are ways via the atom smasher.
And I have not started to run into the problem of being completely overrun with trash, which
I think that with this many dwarves we are probably going to get there.
And I am still struggling with my magma dump area.
And I think that it's something to do with needing a refuse stockpile and a dumping zone
in the same tile.
You have to layer those together to get it to work.
So we're still just using garbage piles.