When I checked on it today, she was out of the hospital.
She was there a lot longer than our militia commander whose hand had like exploded.
And she, the child, had had crushed ribs, I think, so she just needed longer in the
hospital.
But when our migrants showed up, there were a couple of proficient doctors.
So now we have a chief medical dwarf, a bone doctor, and a surgeon.
So they treated both the child and the militia commander, and both of them have now been
released from the hospital.
Doing pretty well.
I'm going to keep an eye on those, the four adults, as well as the child who was left
for dead.
So we have the angry militia commander who is azoom glaze inches.
She is in the 7 out of 7 dreadful mood.
She is extremely angry.
She's not in the hospital anymore.
I retired her from being militia commander while she was so injured.
I'm not sure what to do with her now.
I'd rather not have to banish her because I would like to hang on to those original
four dwarves.
So I'm going to look into her interests and stuff and see if we can't cheer her up.
We have logam tongue spear.