just turn them off in world generation.
It's something to think about,
and I do feel a little bit like it's a challenge
that I need to learn to handle,
but also like it's a game, you know?
I'm here to have fun.
Right, and if I don't wanna deal with water in that way,
then I don't have to,
but with the stream drying up in the winter,
yeah, I don't know.
So I'm gonna figure that out maybe.
The other thing that I'm gonna start doing
is building just a bunch of cage traps,
because I've already caught a couple
of other cavern creatures in those,
and I'm not really sure what to do with them
once I have them caged,
so I just sort of put them outside.
Yeah. Good luck.