Yeah, I think that's a really good strategy.
And once you get kind of a stable location like that,
you can start to kind of expand outward and build walls
and keep yourself protected that way if you want to turtle a bit.
Yeah.
And there's nothing wrong with that.
And by getting down to the magma and easy access
to the various metal ores and all that,
you can really start pumping out a lot of tradable goods
and really bring the value of your fort up
and start to get yourself in a position to become the mountain home.
Yeah.
And this is, you know, sort of the way the game was meant to be played.
Again, I feel bad saying this because, as we've talked about,
Dwarf Fortress.