Yeah, that's fair. That's fair. I have done it. It works fine. I was able to sort of,
grep is the term, do find, find replace through it for some different bits of information,
but it's definitely going to have to wait for the DFHack guys to update the Legends Mode viewer
software that's out there before I think it'll be super readable to people. But using that,
I was able to find out stuff about the various gods that we have going on and all that sort of
thing. And actually, it'd be pretty interesting to combine the information that comes from that
with the information that our Discord member wrote. Oh, yeah. Right. He wrote that little
script to pull out information using kind of a subsystem in DFHack online. I think the information
that he pulled out with that is actually not in the accidental export. Oh, wow. All right.
Or some of it is and some of it isn't from what I could see, but I need to investigate that further
and see about maybe we can merge all this information together or do something like that.