Well, let's take a minute and talk about that, because I was also left with a bad situation
with my five dwarves and seven children.
So I actually turned to our listeners in the Discord and got some good advice, and I really
didn't want to give up this fort and was like, if I lose it, I'm still going to go reclaim
it because I really like this location.
So I went through and turned off all the work orders, except I think...
We had a lot of drinks, we had a lot of food, so I didn't even have a work order going there.
I think I might have left gem cutting going because we have a legendary gem cutter, and
I was like, well, eventually we will get a merchant and I can spend gems and get some
migrants.
And it went pretty well, actually.
I also made sure to finish walling off our caverns so that nothing else could come in,
because at some point we did have two giant olms wander in as I was walling us off, and
nothing really bad happened.
They did eventually kill them, but somehow in that, in the walling off, we lost another
expedition leader.
I have no idea how he died.
I'm assuming he must have gotten walled out or was secretly killed by a giant olm, but
I think I would have gotten a notification about that.
I just got the pop-up that he had been missing for a week.
And then we were on to our third expedition leader.
So I kind of just let the fort run for a while.
We eventually did get merchants.
They didn't have very much good stuff, but I just bought all of it in the hopes of getting
some migrants.