Yeah and so sometimes that can be like we've talked about with like a project fort or a particular
location that you want to explore but sometimes you just find a dwarf who's interesting like the
one you had that zany yeah that's anyone back at the beginning yeah yeah and so you can kind of
follow them and and see who they interact with and what they do and if that becomes a story
and like I mentioned for the story at the end of the episode that I wrote I just was really like
taken with this idea of just a totally normal couple finding themselves just suddenly royalty
with solid gold floors and um and like the juxtaposition of that with the fact that they're
eating like long biscuits and this mediocre food and none of that stuff changes but here we're
royalty so uh it's more like a little vignette than a story but that that is kind of how those
things can get started and and thinking about that I um was thinking about like your power
couple how did you how did that come to speak to you?