Yeah, exactly. And I think that Dwarf Fortress in particular is really interesting for this
type of exercise because you can tell a grand epic story of this settlement, but you can also
tell these tiny little stories of dwarven day-to-day life. I had really, really wanted
to tell a story of a child dwarf who had lost her parents. Oh, she survived the demon attack
that both of her parents died to. And she was despairing and wandering, but she would still
go and play make-believe. But then ultimately, she didn't do anything. She would sleep,
she would play make-believe, she'd eat, and that was it. And so I ended up not really being able to
write a story about that because there's just nothing there. So sometimes there are dead ends
in that way too, in the same way that you start a fort with this idea that you're going to do this
huge project, but then you don't have the resources you need, or you keep getting attacked by zombies
or something like that, and it just defies you.