the 8th annual tournament.
Tournament.
Hope it's the 8th, I didn't actually write it down this time.
But we're just going to run with 8th.
Sure.
So, over at Bay12Games, you can read the entire fight yourself,
but the tournament wound up with Logum Branch Syrup, the Wolverine Man,
versus Knifing Around, the Hori Marmot Woman,
which I remember we talked about both of them previously.
Yeah.
Katana Blows from Logum gave him an early lead,
and Knifing Around was never able to recover,
losing legs, feet, arms, and hands every time she tried to attack Logum.
Eventually, after one last lunge cost her what remained of her left arm,
Knifing Around's blood-streaked body slammed to the ground and failed to rise again.
Congratulations to Logum Branch Syrup, champion of the 8th tournament.