Truly, it is a blessing for our family.
I love the dining room especially.
The dining room was rather ironic, though.
Fully engraved gold floors and a jet table did not improve the quality of giant cave-swallow
lung biscuits and the same old dwarven wine, but Adil saw now that Ral did not want to
hear that.
There had been nothing wrong with their old quarters.
They were spacious, fully engraved, good honest mudstone floors and walls.
But Adil had been unsatisfied.
Ral was right about that.
They had their children and both were healthy and very happy.
Ral was certainly happy, mining and hauling and socializing in the tavern.