Their ascension to the nobility made as little sense as the sudden disappearance of the reptile
men that had ruined his health and killed so many.
It seemed, sometimes, that whatever divine forces ruled Wet-Ringed, they were as arbitrary
and thoughtless as the fall of the snow outside.
He shouldn't question it, he knew, but somehow it deepened his sense of aimlessness.
The purposelessness of it all hung over his mind like a stagnant gray miasma.
But Ral, glowing with her glorious transformation into royalty, did not notice his malaise.
She nuzzled his beard.
This will be the start of a new future for us, and for Wet-Ringed.
Adil forced a smile and squeezed her tightly.
What do you plan to do with your new power? he asked, trying to sound playful.
Hmm, Ral said.
Well, I think I'll order the construction of gauntlets.