Oh, I should sic the cat on it.
I would be devastated if that cat died, though, so I'll let it run.
It's still qualified or counted as a city, even though we didn't get promoted from barony
to duchy or whatever.
58 dwarves remain, and the traders arrived, and I was able to buy enough drinks to replace
all of the drinks that had been burned up, and some plump helmets and meat and stuff,
so we'll see what happens.
Yes, the baroness's husband, who is the main character of the story that I wrote and recorded
earlier today, is dead, presumably burnt to a crisp.
He's listed, I think, as missing, which all of the ones who were just incinerated are,
I think, listed as missing.