Yeah, so it's pretty easy.
I don't think that it was a calm or peaceful
or whatever location.
Like I expected to have wildlife
and we really, really haven't.
Not even, not outdoors or in the caves.
So it's seemed to be a peaceful location
and I might end up regret, end up regretting choosing it.
But the nice thing about it so far,
even though I haven't found a lot of metals yet,
we have a lot of the really beautiful, colorful stones.
So we've got a ton of jet.
So that looks really cool in combination
with like marble and microclime.
And I have like a really neat bedroom setup
with like four long spokes off a staircase
and the rooms are kind of staggered off of it.
And they're all in those colors
and just without really any work from me,
it looks pretty cool.