Oh, okay, gross. At any rate, I'm going to have to look up, what is beekeeping called?
Apiary?
Apiary, yeah.
Anyway, yes, got to look up apiary in the wiki. So maybe next time I can report back about my
adventures in Dwarven Honey. But the biggest problem that I've had actually so far is related
to the caverns in that I have been really diligent with my last few fort ventures about walling off
where we're living in the caverns so that we don't get all the cave people invading constantly.
The caverns at this fort are really like craggy and hilly, so the terrain is just
spanning multi-levels. And it's going to be really, really hard to wall in, I think, because
those walls will have to extend like this.