Yeah, you know, after I had a couple weeks off from the game, just kind of taking a break from that,
because it's good to not burn out on, you know, even fun things. I went back to Bellblade,
I booted it up, I was looking around. I couldn't remember. Like, there was this guild hall that I
was building, and I couldn't remember who it was for, and there was just a lot going on, but nothing
really was happening, and it was all very defensible, and I was just like, you know, I feel kind of done
with this one. Like, it's doing really well, it's a metropolis. And then there was another migrant
wave that was pushing the population up over 170. And I was, like, thinking about how much work it
was going to be to get the bedrooms and everything and furnished for all that, and I was just like,
yeah, it's time. I just retired it. And, you know, I might check back in on them, kind of like I did
with Curlkey, but I don't feel too remorseful. I was kind of attached to a few individuals there,
but also, like, they don't really exist. So I wasn't that sad.