this in 10 seconds.
Oh, well we have talked about Legends Mode before, but Legends Mode is when you export
your world save and you can look at all the people and the history of cities and civilizations
and things.
It's very fun.
So I looked up the history and goings on of Bellblade and as I was saying, none of my
beloved characters had really done anything interesting like Rith Guildthunders, that
unhappy child whose parents died in a demon attack.
There's no additional information about her, so I'm assuming she's just still wandering
around despondently.
Whatever.
But I did notice that there had been a change in leadership a little bit and in the late
autumn of 134, I believe I left in like summer of 134.