Yeah, and a different dwarf replaced her as the bookkeeper. So I had wondered, like I saw that
she stopped being bookkeeper and I was like, what on earth did they do? Well, they made her champion.
And browsing through Legends mode even more, it looks like she was a resident of my fort's tomb
dens, rasp boat, and Krolky at the very least. Like those are the ones that I like remembered
and stuck out to me. So she, I guess, has migrated around in her life and then came out to this far
continent. And now I'm wondering, it's a different civilization, but she has changed civilizations
before if she will come to Wet Ring. So I am I'm going to be on the lookout for her.
She is married and has two children. And her husband's goal was to start a family.
Oh, hers was to master a skill. So hopefully she can do that as fort champion.
But her husband, Bim Frosty Fountains, is quite a martial leader. Yes, I love that name,
Bim Frosty Fountains. But he's led several attacks for the Razor of Socketing, which is
that other civilization that I forgot to start my new fort in for continuity. But he lost all of
those attacks except one, I think. So it's a good thing that like his goal is not to be a successful
military leader and is instead to have a family because now they have two children. They seem happy.