Yeah, the options in this one are a devil, a fey, or an outer god.
And an outer god is, again, Cthulhu, but not the mind flayer Cthulhu.
Yes.
So I chose the outer gods because I thought that sounded fun.
It's kind of been interesting listening to other people talk about it, that background,
because your background plays a lot into the game.
It does.
It causes various plot beats to happen sooner or gives you different options.
And other people I've heard who have chosen devil and fey, they hear from their patrons,
their warlocks, and they hear from their patrons all the time.
I have not heard a word from my patron.
Two times I've run into a situation where it says
it's given me the option to call upon my patron, and I have, and I just get a dial tone.