Yeah. Are people racist? A little bit. Yeah, as a tiefling, I've encountered some in-game racism,
especially at the beginning sequence with the druids, because they were in direct conflict
with some tiefling refugees, and there's an invasion from the goblins coming, and they want
to kick the tieflings out of their camp and just protect the grove, and you have to make some
decisions early on, like, am I on the side of the druids? Am I on the side of the tieflings? Do I
want to kill this potentially corrupt druid leader? Hell, do I want to side with the goblins
and take over this grove and become, you know, more or less evil? So I am not... it's funny,
like, I'm not really role-playing as, like, oh, you know, I'm playing, like, an ingenue or
something like that, but I'm mostly just making choices that I feel comfortable with on this first
play, and on another I will create a character with more of a personality of its own. So I opted
to... I wanted to help the tieflings, and I didn't feel good about just murdering a woman that, even
though she was threatening to kill a child, I didn't just feel good in this game of my first act
basically being murder.