I have not looked up the persuasive yet. So that will be to, to do be continued on the persuasive.
And then my other final note is that, like, I've been feeling a little bit of dwarf burnout,
I hate to confess, but I was talking to someone in a different discord who was saying that he
had never seen the game. And could I share my screen? And so I did. And these three guys in
this other discord who had never played the game or watching, and hearing they're just like
overwhelmed and delight at the things in Dwarf Fortress was really, really refreshing. So like,
oh my gosh, that's your world map and like all the details. And then I was sort of doing a fort
tour. And they saw the many, many, many trapped creatures that I have caught in cage traps,
and then just put to the basement for lack of a better thing to do with them.
And was asked the question, ma'am, why do you have a gulag in your basement?
And then they enjoyed seeing like the thoughts of all the traumatized creatures in cages.