Both of those were really interesting in what they were trying to do because Pillars of Eternity was where you would set up your own castle that you would slowly build up and do quests around the area and all that sort of stuff.
And then Tyranny was kind of interesting because it was one of the first ones recently that tried
really hard to not have a super good evil system so much as you just had choices to make and they
would have influence. But honestly Tyranny kind of steered a little too much in my mind to the
grimdark side of things. It was a little, I wouldn't say it was Game of Thrones like,
but it was that sort of grimdark like there were rapes and assaults and all that sort of thing in
it. And it just wasn't really my jam. I never bought it. But when I saw people playing Baldur's
Gate 3 I was like, wow, this seems to have a good sense of humor. This seems to be the realistic
like 5e performance. And so I initially said no because I didn't want to steal it away from you.
But after seeing people play it for a while I was like, yeah, no, I need to give this a try.
I booted it up and I think, well you first booted it up and I think you just sat and played for 5 hours.