Okay, okay, you gotta let me talk about my caged elk birds.
So like I said, I had seven.
That was actually, I think, six female and one male,
but you know, good enough.
Although now we're down to five
because I did run out of food.
Sorry, half-trained elk birds, but you got it.
And one of them, some of its bones
got turned into an artifact.
Ooh.
Yeah.
So they were in their cages.
I put them in, I made like a little animal training room.
And the trainer went presumably into there
and fed them little bits of food
and turned them into trained elk birds.
So at that point, I assigned the male
and one of the females to a pasture,
hoping to get new baby elk birds.