Not even a little bit, but it was really funny for me.
So eventually I put her in a cage again
and replaced her with a more bittable female.
Oh no, it's terrible sounding.
So according to the wiki,
elk birds can be really hard to breed.
So I don't have really high hopes
for having a permanent army of elk birds,
but fingers crossed.
And I might get some drunions and bug bats
trained for pets just for fun.
But in order to really get them to be pets,
you have to take them through nine levels of training
from wild to domesticated.
The value of the pet is somewhere assigned to them
that I found on the wiki.
That determines how much time it takes to train them.
So elk birds, for example, are very low value pets
and are trained quickly
versus something I'm assuming like a unicorn
is a high value pet and would take a lot longer
and more skill.
Makes sense.
Wild animals that you've caged and started training
require ongoing training to hold on to their knowledge.
So if you stop training them,
they'll just revert to at least semi-wild.
But then if they have babies,
those babies will be domesticated.
Hooray.