They talked about it some in an interview
with the Dwarf Fortress team, so Zac and Tarn,
and the Caves of Qud team,
part of the PC Gamer Chat Log podcast,
we'll include that in the show notes,
where they talked about the plans for Adventure Mode,
how chat GPT, GPT-4 stuff is influencing
kind of the creation of more content
within Dwarf Fortress, Cave of Qud.
And just kind of about the respective games
and their philosophies, because Caves of Qud
is kind of like an Adventure Mode,
is like what Dwarf Fortress Adventure Mode is,
except it has a built-in story
that you're not pushed through,
but being gently encouraged to follow.
Interesting.
And Caves of Qud, I've played on stream a time or two,
and it's fun.
Cool.
So I think that's everything I had.