It really is, I was quite surprised.
So I could not figure out why we didn't have any food
because we were farming and we were farming,
like I assumed, you know, plump helmets are all.
But then I realized that I had also turned off
plant gathering when I was trying to turn the fort around
so that people could like rest and recover and feel happy
and not be out gathering plants.
So I realized that, turned it on,
it immediately started helping.
But then as Dwarf Fortress is,
a giant Kia stole a step ladder.
No, correction, a giant Kia stole the step ladder.
There's only one in the fort.
There was only one in the fort,
out from under the dwarves gathering in a tree.