Yes, so that was okay, and we haven't seen any forgotten beasts yet.
I'm glad about that because, especially because we're still working on our defenses. In the caverns,
my trap system has worked really, really well, and
we have the aforementioned plump helmet men and
blind cave ogres, some bug bats, and six druunians, which are a large
quadruped with a mane circling its man-like face and hands at the end of its forelimbs.
It lives underground and is fond of raiding the supplies of cavern outposts.
I've never encountered them, but now I have six of them in cages.
We also have captured seven elk birds, and
I have started training them.