But I like the idea of trying to make some of my forts a little prettier.
And remember, I went through that whole thing where I was like,
what's that pink rock?
And I had to go through and find what was pink and try to make doors and things
out of the pink rock just to make it pretty.
So I didn't have enough of whichever one I was using.
Yeah, I think that's rock crystal.
I could have been rock salt. Rock salt. Rock salt.
Right. Rock crystal.
And there's another one that looks pink, but I had some of whatever it was.
And that was kind of fun.
And then in Lore Copper Leopard's office, I put,
I don't remember which mineral it was, but it like blue flooring.
And it's really very pretty.
Oh, that sounds nice.