Not the D&D dungeon master.
Oh, okay.
Or the other one.
You're going somewhere else completely.
But I tell you all these facts about Lore so you can understand his main rival in the Fort,
which is our new Baron and formerly Chief Medical Dwarf, Ushat Seedlabored.
He was made Baron while Lore Goldenwhip was off on the attack on Doomfeat,
Goblin Pit Doomfeat, and we got promoted.
Yeah.
Partly as a result of that fight, partly as a result of settling the Dwarven Hillock,
and he was chosen to become Baron, Ushat Seedlabored.
As time has gone on, those two have developed a rivalry.
Partly, this is because of religious differences.