Well, mine are across the hallway from the temple, which seems...
Appropriate.
Yeah, you know, you go pray, you go think about your dead friends.
And unfortunately that hasn't really helped, the memorializing, I mean.
But I'm also trying some more practical things, like lots of engraving, lots of smoothing,
putting down some floors here and there to make things pretty, because, you know, dwarves
like things to be pretty.
And I've improved some bedrooms, both with the engraving and floors, and then I think
I added a chest to a few bedrooms so that they have more place to store their stuff.
Although some of them are unhappy because they haven't gotten any new stuff for a while.