Fair enough.
So that's the water element.
The other thing that I wanted to talk about a little bit was choosing your location visually
rather than necessarily scanning for things that you want.
I put down my embark location sort of in the crook of a Y of a brook.
I was like, oh, we'll have plenty of good water streams.
And I've had good luck with fishing being a primary food source.
And then you get all the shells and it's a good starting industry.
But when I got into the embark location, it was like just a black screen because it put
them in like this teeny little hollow in the midst of a bunch of hills, which at first
was just like, oh, no, what have I done?
But then I realized I just tunneled sideways into the hill and it was totally it was in
some ways easier.
But I was a little bit worried about caravans and things getting to us, especially because
for me, at least the good location was really far from most of the Dwarven civilizations.
Like my nearest neighbors are elves and more elves and more elves.
The elves are.