No, because I have a fisher dwarf fishing in the caverns.
That was the next thing I was gonna say
is I hit cavern really, really early.
I think that it's only, it might be like negative 10,
and I only started at like a four, plus four.
So I hit cavern really early.
It had lots of fungus.
It had water.
So I immediately plopped down a bunch of farms,
put all the animals in the caverns,
cut down a bunch of mushroom trees,
started fishing, and we were good to go.
The other really odd thing is that we have not come across
any cavern dwellers.
Well, that's nice.
Yeah, and I don't know if it's because
some of the cavern I haven't accessed.
So my openings are just not connected
to the caverns in that way.
And maybe in this shallow cavern
where we're just ran amok, there's none.
It could be that.
And as I had been chasing down metals and things,
I've been really careful to leave a wall
between the cavern and where we're going
so that I don't end up with the constant Batman
sieging from within,
because that can be really a pain.