No, I don't remember. I think the name started with a U, which among dwarves is, you know,
half of them. So the, I guess, I mean, most of everything that's come out of Curlkey has been
really positive. We have a lot of artifacts, including a table that features engraving of
boogeymen. Boogeymen, plural. Not just one boogeyman, many boogeymen. And I put that in
the tavern. They love their tavern. They are always partying in there. We had a minotaur come.
It was very scary. You get the little scary beast image notification in the upper left. He came. He
ran inside before I could stop him and was promptly murdered by someone who just happened
to be at the trade depot. Huh. He did take out one dwarf and that dwarf's pet bunny.
Aw. So that was pretty sad. I might carve a slab for the pet bunny. Might as well. Yeah. So I,
I have to think that maybe the mirthful location is just a little on the easy side.
And there's nothing wrong with that. Danger. Yeah. I'm having a lot of fun,
so I might see how far I can get in terms of barony and all that stuff before I leave this one.