sometimes I feel like that the number of zombies seemed to increase.
So maybe the necromancer didn't leave immediately.
But, um, I decided I wasn't ready to just abandon rag dreams.
Um, even though the traders and guests and things obviously couldn't make it.
So we were just closed in with the extremely overpowered hatch in the ground
that kept anything from getting in.
Um, so I got the idea to build a bunch of cage traps surrounding the staircase.
And then I would open the top hatch, let the zombies into that level with a hatch
to keep them from going lower.
And, um, then we deal with them in batches and take them off and drop
them into magma or whatever, whatever you do with zombies.
Um, but then I realized that, um, they, they weren't like opening
the hatch and coming in anyway.
I kind of had to beat them with some dwarves, which was terrible, but, um,
I was willing to accept the sacrifice.
So I opened the hatches, um, and then found out that the, um, the, the cage
traps were around the stairs and the zombies just zoomed right down the
stairs without ever getting trapped.
As this was going on, the internet was dropping repeatedly and I was struggling
to see that it was dropping because the software that I was using for Twitch
was not telling me when it was dropping.
And I had no idea.
So I'd just be happily talking up here to myself and you would have to come
up into my studio and say, Hey, by the way, that, that stream dropped again.